The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Invader, I will take your life !
He's Core Formation ?
Formation, activate !
Note: Wang Lin got this formation from the Evil Devil Sect disciples he killed.
Can this formation trap a Core Formation cultivator ?
If you were at Peak Late stage,
then this formation
might have stood a chance against me.
It's a shame you're just a Middle stage Foundation Establishment...
Go !
I will kill you, I will kill you.
I'll slash you to death, bastard !
Foundation Establishment brat,
taste the power of Core Formation !
That guy is cunning.
He would never attack
without absolute certainty.
Could it be...
Xu Liguo, what are you waiting for ?
Do you want to die ?
I knew it...
Damn heavens,
why is this my fate ?
But... If I devour a Core Formation cultivator,
my power might increase dramatically !
Then I will be able to kill my ungrateful master
and I'll be free
to roam through
heaven and earth !
I'm done playing with you !
Your soul is restricted
and you can't escape my Bloodfiend Demon Formation.
This Divine Sense is mine !
Stop this !
No no no
I'll give it back...
Come back
or I will kill you immediately.
If the Evil Devil Sect's jade slip is correct
then absorbing a Golden Core can boost my cultivation.
This is my key to Peak Late stage Foundation Establishment.
Where is he ?
Find him !
Understood !
The spiritual energy in a Golden Core is immense !
Unfortunately, I can only absorb 10% of this energy
since I didn't cultivate the Great Freedom Asura Art.
Congratulations Master on reaching Peak Late stage Foundation Establishment.
Wang Lin\NPeak Late stage\NFoundation Establishment
Scout ahead
instead of talking.
Master...
You haven't told me
where we're going to.
The Burning Fire Alliance.
Oh..
Very good.
At this rate,
you might even win the Heaven Separating Pill.
However,
I'm wondering how
you were able to advance so quickly.
Just before,
you were Middle stage Foundation Establishment.
It's embarrassing but
Junior encountered a severely injured Core Formation cultivator.
To be able to defend myself,
I had no choice but to take his Golden Core.
That's how my cultivation rose
to Peak Late stage Foundation Establishment.
This is the second map piece.
When you fulfill your next task,
come to me
for the third piece.
Country of Xuanwu
Burning Fire Country
Nan Dou City
Sea of Devils
The continent's information
must be on that final map piece.
Thank you, Senior.
Wang Lin,
the cultivators of Xuanwu have gathered
so a great battle is approaching.
Whether you are seeking
the map or the Heaven Separating Pill,
the next few days
will be your best opportunity.
Fellow cultivators !
Fellow cultivators,
our Nascent Soul physical bodies were attacked
and the Country Sealing Formation
has shattered...
The Fire Spirit Beasts are coming !
The Heaven Defying Bead absorbed the Fire Spirit Beast King
so I'm sure the Fire Spirit Beasts will look everywhere for me.
I can't stay here anymore.
Forget the Heaven Separating Pill,
I need the map in order to return to Zhao.
Yang Xiong,
why were you looking for me ?
Senior...
Master, I've done what you asked.
As for my Soul Blood...
I'm sorry.
Ancestor Feng Luan is my mother.
When she saw me,
she knew something was wrong.
So...
I didn't come for your Soul Blood.
I just need your help for something.
Is it about the map ?
My homeland is far away
and I have no way to find it
without a map.
Then help me kill 2 people.
You know them both.
The first is Ma Liang's childhood friend Xu Si
and the other
is that scoundrel Zhou An who's been with her.
I trust you, Senior.
Come back in an hour
and I'll give you the map.
Deal.
Ma Liang...
This is the last thing I can do for you...
Disgusting...
Who would've thought Ma Liang
would actually return alive ?
Are you
still thinking about him ?
Of course not.
Don't you feel that
since he returned,
he seemed like a different person ?
A mere Foundation Establishment cultivator
being so high profile
cannot end well for him.
Ma Liang,
I will kill the person you once loved
but that has heartlessly abandoned you.
I wonder how you would feel
if you were still here.
Xu Si... Xu Si !
You two were doomed anyway.
Not just because of my promise to Zhou Zihong,
but because
I will never leave any potential danger behind anymore.
The Sea of Devils
is like hell on earth.
It's filled with a malevolent aura.
The cultivators here
are cunning like foxes,
treacherous and ruthless.
Most of them come from the outside
but their rebellious nature
or their bloody past
forced them to flee.
They all end up gathering here
in the Sea of Devils where everyone cultivates
like a Devil.
This Sea of Devils is too dangerous.
I'm only at Peak Late stage Foundation Establishment...
If I want to return to Zhao,
it will be extremely difficult.
Young lady,
I have killed every single member of your squad.
Do you think you can run away ?
The Luo River Sect has been testing poisons for generations,
if you're not afraid...
It's too dangerous for a girl to do alchemy and test poisons.
Wouldn't it be awesome to have someone
for Dual Cultivation ?
He's Middle stage Core Formation.
I can't handle him without
the Bloodfiend Demon Formation.
A Junior who knows the Earth Escape Technique ?
Since we've met,
I might as well kill you too !
Senior !
Save me.
Senior,
he's from Xuanwu's Dual Cultivation Sect.
He knows that I have a Heaven Separating Pill.
If Senior can save me...
He can't save you.
Do you really have a Heaven Separating Pill ?
We are both from the Burning Fire Alliance.
Even if he's a madman,
falling into his hands
is better than being caught by that Core Formation from Xuanwu.
I don't have a complete Heaven Separating Pill,
just a half-finished product.
The Luo River Sect's Heaven Separating Pills
are always half-finished !
It just needs half an hour to refine.
Once a Heaven Separating Pill is completed,
it must be consumed within an hour
or it will be useless.
Are you looking for reinforcements from the Burning Fire Alliance ?
Did I allow you to do that !?
I'm no match for him,
I only have one way
to shake him off.
Senior,
you're going towards the Burning Fire Country.
It must at least be 3 hours
since the formation broke.
Excluding the time for the Nascent Soul
to get back to deliver the message,
The Fire Spirit Beasts
must have already entered Xuanwu.
The game is over for you !
Now is the time !
What's this?
Weren't the Fire Spirit Beasts sealed by the formation ?
Wait, we should report this !
They already know,
don't worry about it.
Shit,
they saw us.
3 days later
He appears to be at Foundation Establishment
but he's been using the Earth Escape for 3 days straight to cross the country.
The Burning Fire Alliance couldn't resist those beasts
so how does he plan to escape them ?
Senior...
This... this is the Sea of Devils !
I know.
Maybe someone in the Sea of Devils
might be able to stop the Fire Spirit Beasts.
Besides, the Sea of Devils is thousands of times bigger than the Burning Fire Country.
Even the Fire Spirit Beasts
will struggle to find us behind this thick fog.
Senior,
am I correct ?
Yes.
The Sea of Devils I wanted to avoid
ended up becoming our only way out.
Cold Yin spiritual energy ?
The Sea of Devils is like a wall of ice
that contrasts with the Burning Fire Country's heat.
Everything has a weakness,
this cold fog can suppress Fire Spirit Beasts.
Our priority now
is to find a cave and have me reach Core Formation.
The only way to survive the Sea of Devils
is to have me form my Golden Core
so that I can become the strongest person under Nascent Soul.
Dual Cultivation has multiple meanings. It can just mean a marriage between 2 cultivators.\NBut the second meaning is the exploitation and absorption of spiritual energy through sex (which is the method of the Dual Cultivation Sect that Core Formation cultivator is part of). In that system, the male represents the Yang and the female the Yin, both complementing each other.\N\NIn the event that one is stronger than the other, the weaker (generally the woman) will become the other's "cultivation furnace".\N\NThe term "cultivation furnace" is more widely used for any kind of exploitation of someone else to further one's cultivation.\N\NThat's why he was keeping Li Muwan alive.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?